CAMILA APARICIO

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT



(647) 975-7248



camilaaparicioo@hotmail.com

in linkedin.com/camilaaparicio



www.camilaaparicio.com



Toronto, Ontario

PROFILE

I am a front-end web developer with a passion for building responsive, accessible and engaging websites.

My diverse experiences have taught me how to be a strong team member in a variety of high performing groups and exposed me to experiences requiring logical problem solving and strong communication skills.

Languages: English & Spanish

EDUCATION

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

- Immersive Web Development Certificate
- Intro To Java Script
- Intro to Web Development

UNIVERSITY OF GUELPH-HUMBER

 Honours Bachelor of Applied Science in Social Work | 2012-2016

PROJECTS

MEME IN A GIFFY

Github Repo \ Live Site

HTML \ CSS \ REACT \ FIREBASE \ API

Through group programming, built a website that allows users to generate their own memes by inputting text. Using Firebase database to store memes.

MOVIE SEARCHER

Github Repo \ Live Site

HTML \ CSS \ VANILLA JAVASCRIPT \ API

Through pair programming, built a website that allows for users to search up movies using an API call to fetch data from the IMDB API.

E-COMMERCE SITE

Github Repo \ Live Site

HTML \ CSS \ JavaScript \ REACT \ API

Built an e-commerce site entirely in React using the FakeStore API to fetch data. Users are able to filter through products via categories.

EXPERIENCE

PENSION TECHNICIAN

Morneau Shepell - Feb 2019 - Sept 2021

- Calculated and issued benefit payments in accordance with plan rules and legislation.
- · Answered queries from clients, plan members and trustees, providing relevant information and appropriate follow-up.

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

First Republic Capital - Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

· Liaised with internal and external parties involved with the proceedings in preparation of private placements.

FRONT DESK COORDINATOR

Cactus Club Café - Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

· Coordinated and managed front desk team through effective guidance and strong communication skills in a professional manner in a high volume and demanding environment.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, Command Line, Restful APIs, Firebase, Version Control & Collaboration using Git & GitHub, Web Accessibility, Responsive Web Design, Pair Programing